DECISION ON MY OWN, CONSULTING
WITH MY STAFF, AND REVIEWING THE
INCREDIBLY STRONG EVIDENCE THAT
WE ACCURATE.
SEN. KENNEDY: IN FACT, PRESIDENT
BIDEN AND/OR HIS WHITE HOUSE
STAFF TOLD GENERAL GARLAND TO
PROSECUTE THE PRESIDENT, DIDN'T
HE?
MR. SMITH: AGAIN, I HAVE NO IDEA
ABOUT THAT.
WHAT MY JOB WAS --
SEN. KENNEDY: DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT THAT.
DO YOU BELIEVE IN THE TOOTH
FAIRY?
MR. SMITH: I DO NOT.
SEN. KENNEDY: HOW ABOUT THE
EASTER BUNNY?
MR. SMITH: I NO LONGER BELIEVE
IN THE EASTER BUNNY.
SEN. KENNEDY: DO YOU THINK JIMMY
HOFFA DIED OF NATURAL CAUSES?
MR. SMITH: I DO NOT.
SEN. KENNEDY: NOW, YOU SOUGHT
THE PHONE RECORDS OF A BUNCH OF
U.S. SENATORS, RIGHT?
MR. SMITH: WE SOUGHT THE TOLL
RECORDS, NONCONTENT RECORDS.
SEN. KENNEDY: ANY DEMOCRATS OR
JUST REPUBLICANS?
MR. SMITH: IF PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAD REACHED OUT TO DEMOCRATS --
SEN. KENNEDY: I'M JUST TRYING TO
GET THE FACTS.
WERE THERE ANY DEMOCRATS YOU
SOUGHT THE PHONE RECORDS?
JUST REPUBLICANS, RIGHT?
MR. SMITH: THE TOLL RECORDS THAT
WE SOUGHT WERE RELEVANT TO THE
INVESTIGATION, AND THEY WERE
REPUBLICANS.
SEN. KENNEDY: I'M ASKING YOU.
YOU STALLED ME AGAIN, COUNSELOR,
YOU KNOW THAT.
YOU SOUGHT JUST THE RECORDS OF
REPUBLICANS.
AND YOU KNEW THAT VIOLATED THE
SPEECH AND DEBATE CLAUSE, DIDN'T
YOU?
MR. SMITH: THAT IS INCORRECT.
WE SOUGHT TO COMPLY --
SEN. KENNEDY: DID YOU TAKE IT?
MR. SMITH: I'M SORRY?
SEN. KENNEDY: WERE YOU IN THE
QUAD PLAYING FRISBEE DURING CON
LAW IN HARVARD LAW SCHOOL?
MR. SMITH: I DID TAKE
CONSTITUTIONAL LAW, YES.
SEN. KENNEDY: THEN YOU HAD TO
KNOW IT VIOLATED THE
SPEECH DEBATE CLAUSE.
IN FACT, WHEN YOU WENT TO JUDGE
BOSBERG, YOU DID NOT EVEN TELL
HIM YOU WERE SEEKING THE PHONE
RECORDS OF MEMBERS OF CONGRESS,
DID YOU?
BECAUSE YOU KNEW HE WOULDN'T
AGREE.
HE WOULD SAY, HEY, COUNSELOR,
ANYBODY WHO KNOWS A LAW BOOK
FROM A J. CREW CATALOGUE KNOWS
THIS VIOLATES THE CONSTITUTION.
BUT YOU DIDN'T TELL HIM, DID
YOU?
MR. SMITH: WE SOUGHT
NONDISCLOSURE ORDERS.
SEN. KENNEDY: YOU DIDN'T TELL
HIM, DID YOU?
MR. SMITH: IN SEEKING
NONDISCLOSURE ORDERS, WE DID
NOT.
SEN. KENNEDY: BUT YOU'RE
UNBIASED.
YOU HAVE NO PERSONAL FEELING.
YOU MAKE ME WANT TO THROW UP IN
MY MOUTH.
SEN. DURBIN: MR. CHAIRMAN.
I'D LIKE TO SAY A WORD.
THIS HEARING IS OF